University of Connecticut 1998.0380
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, President's Office Records [Charles C. McCracken, 1930-1935]
undated, 1926-1935.
1998.0380
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
9.0 Linear feet
The records consist of the general correspondence of the President of the College. It is the only extant collection of the papers of the president for this period. The correspondence is concerned with internal administrative matters, major policy issues at the college, with the college's relations with state and federal governments, and with other educational agencies and institutions.
University of Connecticut. President's Office.
Biography
Charles Chester McCracken succeeded Dr. Works in 1930. President McCracken maintained a steady growth of the college and the quality of its programs during the difficult early years of the Depression. The highlight of his years at Storrs was the changing of the name of the institution to Connecticut State College in 1933, which culminated a long campaign by students, alumni and administrators. He left the college in 1935 to accept a position in religious education in Philadelphia, PA.
Scope and Content
The records consist of the general correspondence of the President of the College. It is the only extant collection of the papers of the president for this period. The correspondence is concerned with internal administrative matters, major policy issues at the college, with the college's relations with state and federal governments, and with other educational agencies and institutions.
Arrangement
Series I: Correspondence ( undated, 1926-1935 ) contains incoming and copies of outgoing correspondence documenting the activities of the administration and interests of the President of the institution. Materials pre-dating McCracken's tenure can be found in multiple folders, particularly in the 1930-1931 section, and have been noted in brackets in the folder listing. In addition, some folders contain materials predating the chronological range in which they are located, primarily for those concerning specific issues or individuals that are not consistently represented throughout the Correspondence series.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
The records of the President's Office from 1908 to 1935 were stored in Gulley Hall until about 1960, when they were relocated to the attic of Beach Hall. In 1968 they were brought to the Special Collections Department.
Acquisition Information
The records were transferred to Historical Manuscripts and Archives in August 1979 and were arranged and described in the spring of 1980. In 1995, Special Collections and Historical Manuscripts and Archives merged to form Archives and Special Collections and were relocated to the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center. In 2001, the Presidential records were reprocessed and separated by presidential tenure.
McCracken, Charles C. (Charles Chester).; Administrative Records.; Administrator.; Blueprints.; College presidents--Connecticut.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Notes.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Publications.; School Records.; Speeches.; Universities and colleges--Administration.; University of Connecticut--History.; University of Connecticut--Presidents.; University of Connecticut. Office of the President.
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1926-1935
  - 1930-1931
    - A (Box 1:, Folder 1)
    - Accrediting of C.A.C. (Box 1:, Folder 2)
    - American Council on Education (Box 1:, Folder 3)
    - Association of American Colleges (Box 1:, Folder 4)
    - Board of Trustees of C.A.C., Laws and By-Laws of (Box 1:, Folder 5)
    - C (Box 1:, Folder 6)
    - Carillon
      - General (Box 1:, Folder 7)
      - Meneely and Company (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Carillonneurs and Carillon programs (Box 1:, Folder 9)
    - Chimes
      - J.C. Deagan, Inc., Chicago, Illinois (Box 1:, Folder 10)
      - John Taylor and Co., Loughborough, England (Box 1:, Folder 11)
    - Connecticut Bankers Association (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. [Governor] (Box 1:, Folder 13)
    - Denlinger, Henry K. [English/History] (Box 1:, Folder 14)
    - Ellis, Benjamin W. [1928, Director, Cooperative Extension] (Box 1:, Folder 15)
    - Faculty meeting minutes (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Federal Farm Board (Box 1:, Folder 17)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary of C.A.C. (Box 1:, Folder 18)
    - Fraternities (Box 1:, Folder 19)
    - French, Mildred P. [Dean of Women] (Box 1:, Folder 20)
    - G (Box 1:, Folder 21)
    - Garrigus, H.L. [Animal Husbandry, Farm Superintendent] (Box 2:, Folder 22)
    - General letters to staff [1929] (Box 2:, Folder 23)
    - Gentry, Charles B. [Director of Instruction] (Box 2:, Folder 24)
    - Greene, Arthur F. [Trustee] (Box 2:, Folder 25)
    - Guyer, Roy J. Athletic Director] (Box 2:, Folder 26)
    - Hall, Edward F. [Commission, State Board of Finance and Control] (Box 2:, Folder 27)
    - Horticultural Division (Box 2:, Folder 28)
    - Hypes, J.A. [Sociology] (Box 2:, Folder 29)
    - K (Box 2:, Folder 30)
    - Kirkpatrick, W.F. [Poultry] (Box 2:, Folder 31)
    - Kulp, W. L. [Bacteriology] (Box 2:, Folder 32)
    - L (Box 2:, Folder 33)
    - Landauer, Walter [Genetics] (Box 2:, Folder 34)
    - Longley, Raymond I. [Comptroller] (Box 2:, Folder 35)
    - M (Box 2:, Folder 36)
    - Manchester, Allen W. [Farm Management] (Box 2:, Folder 37)
    - Manchester, Harry G. [Trustee] (Box 2:, Folder 38)
    - Mastrangelo, Vincenzo—case (Box 2:, Folder 39)
    - Military correspondence (Box 2:, Folder 40)
    - Moss, Albert E. [Forestry] (Box 2:, Folder 41)
    - N (Box 2:, Folder 42)
    - National Advisory Committee on Education (Box 2:, Folder 43)
    - National Committee on Education by Radio (Box 2:, Folder 44)
    - New England Association of Collections and Secondary Schools [1929] (Box 2:, Folder 45)
    - New England Council (Box 2:, Folder 46)
    - Newton, Howard D. [Chemistry] (Box 2:, Folder 47)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad (Box 2:, Folder 48)
    - New York, State Education Department (Box 2:, Folder 49)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 2:, Folder 50)
    - Noble, Daniel E. [Radio] (Box 2:, Folder 51)
    - O (Box 2:, Folder 52)
    - P (Box 2:, Folder 53)
    - Perregaux, E. A. [Agricultural Economics] (Box 2:, Folder 54)
    - Perry, Delbert K. [Architect] (Box 2:, Folder 55)
    - R (Box 3:, Folder 56)
    - Radio Committee (Box 3:, Folder 57)
    - Registrar (Box 3:, Folder 58)
    - Resident Physician [1926] (Box 3:, Folder 59)
    - S (Box 3:, Folder 60)
    - Salaries (Box 3:, Folder 61)
    - Scholastic Standing Committee (Box 3:, Folder 62)
    - Student Senate Minutes (Box 3:, Folder 63)
    - U (Box 3:, Folder 64)
    - White, George C. [Dairy] (Box 3:, Folder 65)
  - 1931-1932
    - A (Box 3:, Folder 66)
    - Alsop, Joseph W. [Trustee] (Box 3:, Folder 67)
    - Association of American Universities (Box 3:, Folder 68)
    - B (Box 3:, Folder 69)
    - Brundage, A.J. [Extension Service] (Box 3:, Folder 70)
    - Buckingham, S. McLean [Commissioner of Agriculture] (Box 3:, Folder 71)
    - Buckley, John [Trustee] (Box 3:, Folder 72)
    - Budget (Box 3:, Folder 73)
    - Butterfield, Ernest W. [Commission of Education] (Box 3:, Folder 74)
    - C (Box 4:, Folder 75)
    - Cheney, William Fitch [Mathematics] (Box 4:, Folder 76)
    - Church—Trustee meeting minutes (Box 4:, Folder 77)
    - Commencement (Box 4:, Folder 78)
    - Course of Study Committee (Box 4:, Folder 79)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. [Governor] (Box 4:, Folder 80)
    - Croteau, Arsene [French] (Box 4:, Folder 81)
    - D (Box 4:, Folder 82)
    - Dadourian, H.M. (Mrs.) [Trustee] (Box 4:, Folder 83)
    - Davis, Irving G. [Economics] (Box 4:, Folder 84)
    - Denlinger, Henry K. [English/History] (Box 4:, Folder 85)
    - Dodge, Richard E. [History] (Box 4:, Folder 86)
    - Dole, Sumner A. [Dean of Men] (Box 4:, Folder 87)
    - E (Box 4:, Folder 88)
    - Edel, Walter L. [Dean, School of Engineering] (Box 4:, Folder 89)
    - Ellis, Benjamin W. [Director, Extension Service] (Box 4:, Folder 90)
    - F (Box 4:, Folder 91)
    - Faculty meeting minutes (Box 4:, Folder 92)
    - Farm and Home Week (Box 4:, Folder 93)
    - Federal Farm Board (Box 4:, Folder 94)
    - Federal Radio Commission Hearing (Box 4:, Folder 95)
    - Fenton, Horace J. [Trustee] (Box 4:, Folder 96)
    - Ferguson, F.A. [Physics] (Box 4:, Folder 97)
    - France, Herbert A. [Music] (Box 4:, Folder 98)
    - French, Mildred P. [Dean of Women] (Box 5:, Folder 99)
    - G (Box 5:, Folder 100)
    - Gentry, Charles B. [Director of Instruction] (Box 5:, Folder 101)
      - Memoranda of Conferences (Box 5:, Folder 102)
    - Greene, Arthur F. [Trustee] (Box 5:, Folder 103)
    - Guyer, Roy J. [Athletic Director] (Box 5:, Folder 104)
    - H (Box 5:, Folder 105)
    - Hall, Edward F. [Commission, State Board of Finance and Control] (Box 5:, Folder 106)
    - Harwood, P. Leroy [Trustee] (Box 5:, Folder 107)
    - Hollister, George H. [Trustee] (Box 5:, Folder 108)
    - Hollister, Sherman P. [Horticulture] (Box 5:, Folder 109)
    - Honorary Recognition (Box 5:, Folder 110)
    - Hough, Clifford E. [Trustee] (Box 5:, Folder 111)
    - K (Box 5:, Folder 112)
    - Kirkpatrick, W.F. [Poultry] (Box 5:, Folder 113)
    - L (Box 5:, Folder 114)
    - Lamson, G.H. [Dean, Agricultural Sciences] (Box 6:, Folder 115)
    - Longley, Raymond I. [Comptroller] (Box 6:, Folder 116)
    - M (Box 6:, Folder 117)
    - Manchester, Allen W. [Director, Extension Services] (Box 6:, Folder 118)
    - Manchester, Harry G. [Trustee] (Box 6:, Folder 119)
    - McPheeters, W.H. [Extension, Agricultural Engineer] (Box 6:, Folder 120)
    - Meneely and Company (Box 6:, Folder 121)
    - Military Correspondence (Box 6:, Folder 122)
    - Mimeograph material (Box 6:, Folder 123)
    - Moore, Edmund A. [History] (Box 6:, Folder 124)
    - Moss, Albert E. [Forestry] (Box 6:, Folder 125)
    - N (Box 6:, Folder 126)
    - National Advisory Committee on Education (Box 6:, Folder 127)
    - National Education Association (Box 6:, Folder 128)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 6:, Folder 129)
    - New England Conference on Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 6:, Folder 130)
    - National Committee on Education by Radio (Box 6:, Folder 131)
    - New England Council (Box 6:, Folder 132)
    - New York, State Department of Education (Box 6:, Folder 133)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 6:, Folder 134)
    - Newton, Howard D. [Chemistry] (Box 6:, Folder 135)
    - Noble, Daniel E. [Radio] (Box 6:, Folder 136)
    - P (Box 6:, Folder 137)
    - Perry, Delbert K. [Architect] (Box 7:, Folder 138)
    - Professional improvement of faculty (Box 7:, Folder 139)
    - Prospective students (Box 7:, Folder 140)
    - Salaries (Box 7:, Folder 141)
    - Slate, W.L. [Director, Experiment Station] (Box 7:, Folder 142)
    - Stemmons, Walter [Editor] (Box 7:, Folder 143)
    - Stevens, Alva T. [Vegetable Gardening] (Box 7:, Folder 144)
    - Student Senate
      - Correspondence (Box 7:, Folder 145)
      - Minutes (Box 7:, Folder 146)
    - Switchboard for Armory Stage (Box 7:, Folder 147)
    - T - V (Box 7:, Folder 148)
    - Thwing, James B. [Alumni Association] (Box 7:, Folder 149)
    - W (Box 7:, Folder 150)
    - White, George C. [Dairy] (Box 7:, Folder 151)
    - Wood, Walter C. [Trustee] (Box 7:, Folder 152)
  - 1932-1933
    - A (Box 7:, Folder 153)
    - Accreditation of college (Box 7:, Folder 154)
    - Alsop, Joseph W. [Trustee] (Box 7:, Folder 155)
    - American Council on Education (Box 7:, Folder 156)
    - Angell, James R. [Yale University] (Box 7:, Folder 157)
    - Applications (Box 7:, Folder 158)
    - Association of American Universities (Box 7:, Folder 159)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 8:, Folder 160)
    - Ba - Bh (Box 8:, Folder 161)
    - Bi - Brn (Box 8:, Folder 162)
    - Bingham, Hiram [U.S. Senator] (Box 8:, Folder 163)
    - Boardman, Harold S. [University of Maine] (Box 8:, Folder 164)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Box 8:, Folder 165)
    - Bressler, Raymond G. [ Rhode Island State College] (Box 8:, Folder 166)
    - Britton, W.E. (Box 8:, Folder 167)
    - Bro - Bz (Box 8:, Folder 168)
    - Brown, Benjamin A. [Agronomy] (Box 8:, Folder 169)
    - Brundage, A.J. [Extension Service] (Box 8:, Folder 170)
    - Buckingham, S. McLean [Commissioner of Agriculture] (Box 8:, Folder 171)
    - Buckley, John [Trustee] (Box 8:, Folder 172)
    - Budget Office (Box 8:, Folder 173)
    - Butterfield, Ernest W. [Commissioner of Education, Trustee] (Box 8:, Folder 174)
    - Ca - Cn (Box 8:, Folder 175)
    - Change of name of the college (Box 8:, Folder 176)
    - Change of name—Congratulations (Box 8:, Folder 177)
    - Cheney, William Fitch [Mathematics] (Box 8:, Folder 178)
    - Co - Cz (Box 8:, Folder 179)
    - Commencement Committee (Box 8:, Folder 180)
    - Connecticut University Extension [1927-1932] (Box 8:, Folder 181)
    - Course of Study Committee (Box 9:, Folder 182)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. [Governor] (Box 9:, Folder 183)
    - Croteau, Arsene [French] (Box 9:, Folder 184)
    - D (Box 9:, Folder 185)
    - Dadourian, H.M. (Mrs.) [Trustee] (Box 9:, Folder 186)
    - Davis, Irving G. [Agricultural Economics] (Box 9:, Folder 187)
    - DeCoursey, R.M. [Zoology] (Box 9:, Folder 188)
    - Dodge, Richard E. [History] (Box 9:, Folder 189)
    - Dole, Sumner A. [Dean of Men] (Box 9:, Folder 190)
    - Dorsey, Henry [Agronomy] (Box 9:, Folder 191)
    - E (Box 9:, Folder 192)
    - Edel, Walter L. [Dean, School of Engineering] (Box 9:, Folder 193)
    - Ellis, Benjamin W. [Director, Extension Service] (Box 9:, Folder 194)
    - Elzy, Ruby (Box 9:, Folder 195)
    - F (Box 9:, Folder 196)
    - Faculty meeting minutes (Box 9:, Folder 197)
    - Farm and Home Week (Box 9:, Folder 198)
    - Federal Cuts (Box 9:, Folder 199)
    - Fenton, Horace J. [Trustee] (Box 9:, Folder 200)
    - France, Herbert A. [Music] (Box 9:, Folder 201)
    - French, Mildred P. [Dean of Women] (Box 9:, Folder 202)
    - Ga - Gn (Box 9:, Folder 203)
    - Gentry, Charles B. [Director of Instruction] (Box 10:, Folder 204)
    - Gilman, Ralph L. [Resident Physician] (Box 10:, Folder 205)
    - Go - Gz (Box 10:, Folder 206)
    - Greene, Arthur F. [Trustee] (Box 10:, Folder 207)
    - Griffenhagen and Associates (Box 10:, Folder 208)
    - Guyer, Roy J. [Athletics Director] (Box 10:, Folder 209)
    - Ha - Hd (Box 10:, Folder 210)
    - Hall, Edward F. [Commission of Finance, Trustee] (Box 10:, Folder 211)
    - Harwood, P. Leroy [Trustee] (Box 10:, Folder 212)
    - He - Hz (Box 10:, Folder 213)
    - Hollister, George H. [Trustee] (Box 10:, Folder 214)
    - Hollister, Sherman P. [Horticulture] (Box 10:, Folder 215)
    - Honorary Recognition (Box 10:, Folder 216)
    - Hood Scholarship (Box 10:, Folder 217)
    - Hough, Clifford E. [Trustee] (Box 10:, Folder 218)
    - Hypes, James L. [Sociology] (Box 10:, Folder 219)
    - I - K (Box 10:, Folder 220)
    - Kirkpatrick, William F. [Poultry] (Box 10:, Folder 221)
    - Kulp, Walter L. [Bacteriology] (Box 10:, Folder 222)
    - La - Lh (Box 10:, Folder 223)
    - Land Grant Association (Box 10:, Folder 224)
    - Legislature - 1933, Board of Education (Box 11:, Folder 225)
    - Lewis, Edward M. [ University of New Hampshire] (Box 11:, Folder 226)
    - Li - Lz (Box 11:, Folder 227)
    - Longley, Raymond I. [Comptroller] (Box 11:, Folder 228)
    - Ma - Md (Box 11:, Folder 229)
    - Manchester, Allen W. [Director, Extension Service] (Box 11:, Folder 230)
    - Manchester, Harry G. [Trustee] (Box 11:, Folder 231)
    - May, Mark A. [Agricultural Engineering] (Box 11:, Folder 232)
    - McPheeters, William H. [Agricultural Engineering] (Box 11:, Folder 233)
    - Me - Mz (Box 11:, Folder 234)
    - Military Correspondence (Box 11:, Folder 235)
    - Montgomery, Robert M. (Box 11:, Folder 236)
    - Morrison, Jean (Box 11:, Folder 237)
    - Moss, Albert E. [Forestry] (Box 11:, Folder 238)
    - N (Box 11:, Folder 239)
    - New York, State Education Department (Box 11:, Folder 240)
    - Newmarker, Edward L. [Agronomy] (Box 11:, Folder 241)
    - Newton, Howard D. [Chemistry] (Box 11:, Folder 242)
    - Noble, Daniel E. [Mechanical Engineering, Radio] (Box 11:, Folder 243)
    - O (Box 11:, Folder 244)
    - Office of Education, U.S. (Box 11:, Folder 245)
    - Oliver, Bernard J. [Assistant Comptroller] (Box 11:, Folder 246)
    - P (Box 11:, Folder 247)
    - Perry, Delbert K. [Architect] (Box 11:, Folder 248)
    - R (Box 11:, Folder 249)
    - Registrar (Box 11:, Folder 250)
    - Ritter, William L. [ROTC] (Box 11:, Folder 251)
    - S (Box 12:, Folder 252)
    - Salaries (Box 12:, Folder 253)
    - Scholastic Standing Committee (Box 12:, Folder 254)
    - Slate, William L. [Director, Experiment Station] (Box 12:, Folder 255)
    - Stemmons, Walter [Editor] (Box 12:, Folder 256)
    - Stevens, Alva T. [Vegetable Gardening] (Box 12:, Folder 257)
    - Student Senate minutes (Box 12:, Folder 258)
    - T (Box 12:, Folder 259)
    - Tax Commissioner (Box 12:, Folder 260)
    - Torrey, George Safford [Botany] (Box 12:, Folder 261)
    - Thwing, James B. [Alumni Association] (Box 12:, Folder 262)
    - W (Box 12:, Folder 263)
    - Waugh, Albert [Economics] (Box 12:, Folder 264)
    - White, George C. [Dean of Agriculture] (Box 12:, Folder 265)
    - Whitney, Edwina [Librarian] (Box 12:, Folder 266)
    - Wood, Walter C. [Trustee] (Box 12:, Folder 267)
    - X - Y (Box 12:, Folder 268)
  - 1933-1934
    - A (Box 12:, Folder 269)
    - Applications (Box 12:, Folder 270)
    - Alsop, Joseph W. [Trustee] (Box 12:, Folder 271)
    - American Council on Education (Box 12:, Folder 272)
    - Athletics—College council (Box 12:, Folder 273)
    - Athletic Department—Criticism (Box 13:, Folder 274)
    - Athletic Committee—Mr. Kinsey (Box 13:, Folder 275)
    - Attorney General (Box 13:, Folder 276)
    - B (Box 13:, Folder 277)
    - Board of Education, State (Box 13:, Folder 278)
    - Buckley, John [Trustee] (Box 13:, Folder 279)
    - Butterfield, Ernest W. [Trustee] (Box 13:, Folder 280)
    - C (Box 13:, Folder 281)
    - Commencement Committee (Box 13:, Folder 282)
    - Comptroller, State (Box 13:, Folder 283)
    - Connecticut Congress of Parents and Teachers (Box 13:, Folder 284)
    - Connecticut University Extension Committee (Box 13:, Folder 285)
    - Course of Study Committee (Box 13:, Folder 286)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. [Governor] (Box 13:, Folder 287)
    - D (Box 13:, Folder 288)
    - Dadourian, H.M. (Mrs.) [Trustee] (Box 13:, Folder 289)
    - Davis, Irving G. [Economics] (Box 13:, Folder 290)
    - Dodge, Richard E. [History] (Box 13:, Folder 291)
    - Dole, Sumner A. [Dean of Men] (Box 13:, Folder 292)
    - E (Box 13:, Folder 293)
    - Edel, Walter L. [Dean, School of Engineering] (Box 13:, Folder 294)
    - Ellis, Benjamin W. [Director, Extension Service] (Box 13:, Folder 295)
    - F (Box 14:, Folder 296)
    - Faculty meeting minutes (Box 14:, Folder 297)
    - Faculty, Training and experience of (Box 14:, Folder 298)
    - Farm and Home Week Committee (Box 14:, Folder 299)
    - Fenton, Horace J. [Trustee] (Box 14:, Folder 300)
    - French, Mildred P. [Dean of Women] (Box 14:, Folder 301)
    - G (Box 14:, Folder 302)
    - Game Propagation and Management [More Game Birds in America, 1931-1932] (Box 14:, Folder 303)
    - Garrigus, Harry L. [Animal Husbandry] (Box 14:, Folder 304)
    - Gentry, Charles B. [Director of Instruction] (Box 14:, Folder 305)
    - Gilman, Ralph L. [Resident Physician] (Box 14:, Folder 306)
    - Graduate students from Connecticut State College (Box 14:, Folder 307)
    - Greene, Arthur F. [Trustee] (Box 14:, Folder 308)
    - Guyer, Roy J. [Athletic Director] (Box 14:, Folder 309)
    - H (Box 14:, Folder 310)
    - Hall, Edward F [Commissioner, State Board of Finance and Control] (Box 14:, Folder 311)
    - Holden, Oliver (Box 14:, Folder 312)
    - Hollister, George H. [Trustee] (Box 14:, Folder 313)
    - Hollister, Sherman P. [Horticulture] (Box 14:, Folder 314)
    - Honorary Recognition (Box 14:, Folder 315)
    - Hough, Clifford E. [Trustee] (Box 14:, Folder 316)
    - Hypes, James L. [Sociology] (Box 15:, Folder 317)
    - I - K (Box 15:, Folder 318)
    - King, Olcott F. [Trustee] (Box 15:, Folder 319)
    - Kirkpatrick, William F. [Poultry] (Box 15:, Folder 320)
    - L (Box 15:, Folder 321)
    - Land Grant College Association (Box 15:, Folder 322)
    - Land Grant College Meeting—November (Box 15:, Folder 323)
    - Leisner, August [English] (Box 15:, Folder 324)
    - Lewis, Edward M. [University of New Hampshire] (Box 15:, Folder 325)
    - Longley, Raymond I. [Comptroller] (Box 15:, Folder 326)
    - M (Box 15:, Folder 327)
    - Manchester, Harry G. [Trustee] (Box 15:, Folder 328)
    - May, Mark A. [Agricultural Engineering] (Box 15:, Folder 329)
    - McPheeters, William H. [Agricultural Engineering] (Box 15:, Folder 330)
    - Military Correspondence (Box 15:, Folder 331)
    - Moore, Edmund A. [History] (Box 15:, Folder 332)
    - N (Box 15:, Folder 333)
    - New York State Education Department (Box 15:, Folder 334)
    - Newton, Howard D. [Chemistry] (Box 15:, Folder 335)
    - Newmarker, Edward L. [Alumni Association] (Box 15:, Folder 336)
    - O (Box 15:, Folder 337)
    - Oliver, Bernard J. [Assistant Comptroller] (Box 15:, Folder 338)
    - P (Box 15:, Folder 339)
    - Pension Committee (Box 15:, Folder 340)
    - R (Box 15:, Folder 341)
    - Radio (Box 15:, Folder 342)
    - Registrar (Box 16:, Folder 343)
    - S (Box 16:, Folder 344)
    - Salaries (Box 16:, Folder 345)
    - Scholarship Loan Committee (Box 16:, Folder 346)
    - Scholarship Standing Committee (Box 16:, Folder 347)
    - Seckerson, Howard A. (Box 16:, Folder 348)
    - Slate, William L. [Director, Experiment Station] (Box 16:, Folder 349)
    - Spencer, Samuel R. [Trustee] (Box 16:, Folder 350)
    - Stemmons, Walter [Editor] (Box 16:, Folder 351)
    - Stockwell, Fred (Mrs.) (Box 16:, Folder 352)
    - Student Senate (Box 16:, Folder 353)
    - T (Box 16:, Folder 354)
    - Teachers College—New Britain (Box 16:, Folder 355)
    - Thwing, James L. [Alumni Association] (Box 16:, Folder 356)
    - U - W (Box 16:, Folder 357)
    - Waugh, Albert E. [Economics] (Box 16:, Folder 358)
    - Whitney, Edwina [Librarian] (Box 16:, Folder 359)
    - White, George C. [Dean, School of Agriculture] (Box 16:, Folder 360)
    - Wood, Walter C. [Trustee] (Box 16:, Folder 361)
  - 1934-1935
    - A (Box 16:, Folder 362)
    - Alcorn, Paul [Librarian] (Box 16:, Folder 363)
    - Alsop, Joseph W. [Trustee] (Box 16:, Folder 364)
    - Alumni Correspondence (Box 16:, Folder 365)
    - American Council on Education (Box 16:, Folder 366)
    - Association of American Universities (Box 16:, Folder 367)
    - Commencement Committee (Box 16:, Folder 368)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. [Governor] (Box 17:, Folder 369)
    - Faculty, Training and experience of (Box 17:, Folder 370)
    - Fenton, Horace J. [Trustee] (Box 17:, Folder 371)
    - Gilbert Farm (Box 17:, Folder 372)
    - Gilman, Ralph L. [Resident Physician] (Box 17:, Folder 373)
    - Hollister, Sherman P. [Horticulture] (Box 17:, Folder 374)
    - Honorary Recognition (Box 17:, Folder 375)
    - Hook, James W. [Trustee] (Box 17:, Folder 376)
    - Hough, Clifford E. [Trustee] (Box 17:, Folder 377)